<resources>
    <string name="app_name">30 Days Of Clean-Eating</string>

    <string name="of_30">of 30</string>

    <string name="dish_about">About:</string>

    <string name="dish1_number">01</string>
    <string name="dish2_number">02</string>
    <string name="dish3_number">03</string>
    <string name="dish4_number">04</string>
    <string name="dish5_number">05</string>
    <string name="dish6_number">06</string>
    <string name="dish7_number">07</string>
    <string name="dish8_number">08</string>
    <string name="dish9_number">09</string>
    <string name="dish10_number">10</string>
    <string name="dish11_number">11</string>
    <string name="dish12_number">12</string>
    <string name="dish13_number">13</string>
    <string name="dish14_number">14</string>
    <string name="dish15_number">15</string>
    <string name="dish16_number">16</string>
    <string name="dish17_number">17</string>
    <string name="dish18_number">18</string>
    <string name="dish19_number">19</string>
    <string name="dish20_number">20</string>
    <string name="dish21_number">21</string>
    <string name="dish22_number">22</string>
    <string name="dish23_number">23</string>
    <string name="dish24_number">24</string>
    <string name="dish25_number">25</string>
    <string name="dish26_number">26</string>
    <string name="dish27_number">27</string>
    <string name="dish28_number">28</string>
    <string name="dish29_number">29</string>
    <string name="dish30_number">30</string>

    <string name="dish1_name">Hearty Chickpea and Spinach Stew</string>
    <string name="dish2_name">Salmon Caesar Salad</string>
    <string name="dish3_name">Black Bean Salad with Grilled Pork Cutlets</string>
    <string name="dish4_name">Roasted Salmon Caprese</string>
    <string name="dish5_name">Healthy Detox Salad</string>
    <string name="dish6_name">Zucchini, Corn and Egg Casserole</string>
    <string name="dish7_name">Chicken with Spinach and Tomato Orzo Salad</string>
    <string name="dish8_name">Salmon-Stuffed Avocados</string>
    <string name="dish9_name">Baked Falafel Sandwiches</string>
    <string name="dish10_name">Chicken and Kale Soup</string>
    <string name="dish11_name">Spinach and Feta-Stuffed Portobello Mushrooms</string>
    <string name="dish12_name">Chicken, Avocado and Quinoa Bowls with Herb Dressing</string>
    <string name="dish13_name">Sheet-Pan Chili-Lime Salmon with Potatoes and Peppers</string>
    <string name="dish14_name">Kale and Avocado Salad with Blueberries and Edamame</string>
    <string name="dish15_name">Zucchini Lasagna Rolls</string>
    <string name="dish16_name">Shrimp-and-Grits-Stuffed Peppers</string>
    <string name="dish17_name">Summer Skillet Vegetable and Egg Scramble</string>
    <string name="dish18_name">Spinach and Herb Turkey Burgers with Portobello "Buns"</string>
    <string name="dish19_name">Tofu and Vegetable Curry with Zucchini Noodles</string>
    <string name="dish20_name">Chopped Cobb Salad with Chicken</string>
    <string name="dish21_name">Vegetarian Slow-Cooker Pozole</string>
    <string name="dish22_name">Herbed Tomato Gratin</string>
    <string name="dish23_name">Philly Cheesesteak-Stuffed Portobello Mushrooms</string>
    <string name="dish24_name">Basil Pesto Pasta with Grilled Vegetables</string>
    <string name="dish25_name">Sheet-Pan Roasted Salmon and Vegetables</string>
    <string name="dish26_name">Hummus-Crusted Chicken</string>
    <string name="dish27_name">Cheesy Spinach-and-Artichoke Stuffed Spaghetti Squash</string>
    <string name="dish28_name">Lemony Lentil Soup with Collards</string>
    <string name="dish29_name">Salmon and Avocado Salad</string>
    <string name="dish30_name">Beef and Bean Chile Verde</string>


    <string name="dish1_description">This satisfying stew comes together in a snap. Mashed chickpeas add body to the broth, and tomato paste adds a savory note without adding too much sodium in this healthy recipe for weight loss.</string>
    <string name="dish2_description">This easy Caesar salad subs creamy Greek yogurt and buttermilk for the traditional egg yolks and olive oil and mixes in mildly bitter radicchio in addition to classic romaine. Using just a small amount of flavorful Parmigiano-Reggiano shaves calories and sodium too.</string>
    <string name="dish3_description">This hearty bean salad is packed with vibrant colors and contrasting textures. Center-cut boneless pork chops (also called pork cutlets) make a convenient and economical protein to round out the meal. This recipe makes one extra cutlet, which can be refrigerated for another use.</string>
    <string name="dish4_description">This oven-ready recipe is snap to prep. Salmon fillets and cherry tomatoes roast side by side on one pan, then they are drizzled with balsamic glaze to pull it all together.</string>
    <string name="dish5_description">Skip the cleanse and eat this instead. Packed with veggies, avocado and seeds, this healthy salad recipe is bursting with vitamins, minerals and antioxidants. Everything can be prepared ahead of time except the avocado. If you love beets, shred one raw and add it to the salad for extra color, crunch and flavor.</string>
    <string name="dish6_description">This healthy casserole is essentially a crustless quiche brimming with fresh summer vegetables. Bake it up for an elegant summer brunch or a casual backyard barbecue.</string>
    <string name="dish7_description">Baked chicken breasts cook in the oven while you mix together a Mediterranean-inspired salad—packed with veggies, whole-wheat orzo and an easy homemade vinaigrette—for a weekend-worthy dinner on the table in under an hour. The leftovers from this healthy 400-calorie meal make a delicious packable lunch for the next day.</string>
    <string name="dish8_description">Canned salmon is a valuable pantry staple and a practical way to include heart-healthy omega-3-rich fish in your diet. Here, we combine it with avocados in an easy no-cook meal.</string>
    <string name="dish9_description">This street-style falafel sandwich is herbaceous, tangy and rich. The falafel gets nice and crispy in the oven, while the veggies inside keep it simple and fresh. Make the tahini sauce ahead of time for easy prep. Wrapping the sandwich in foil makes it a perfect bring-along lunch and helps hold it together for eating on the go.</string>
    <string name="dish10_description">This easy chicken and kale soup will keep you warm on a cold and rainy day or any day that calls for a simple, hearty soup. For convenience, you can make this soup with frozen kale without the need to thaw it beforehand.</string>
    <string name="dish11_description">These stuffed portobello mushrooms have a filling inspired by the Greek spinach pie, spanakopita. To keep them quick, we ditched the phyllo, so they are great for an easy weeknight vegetarian dinner.</string>
    <string name="dish12_description">Arrange the toppings individually on these protein-packed grain bowls so each bite has a contrasting taste and texture. Make big batches of the salad dressing, quinoa and roasted chicken thighs, and you will have healthy meal-prep lunches or dinners for days. Though the chicken thighs take just 15 minutes to prep, you can also make the salads with leftover chicken or store-bought cooked chicken to make prep even faster.</string>
    <string name="dish13_description">Busy weeknights beg for something simple like this salmon sheet-pan dinner. Like the name suggests, it is all cooked on one pan. The potatoes get a head start, followed by sweet bell peppers and finally chili-coated salmon fillets. It is a complete meal with easy cleanup!</string>
    <string name="dish14_description">Bursting with nutrient-rich produce, this California-inspired salad is a delicious and satisfying way to get your vitamins. We love the unique combination of blueberries, edamame and goat cheese.</string>
    <string name="dish15_description">Give lasagna rolls a healthy low-carb makeover with this easy recipe that subs in thinly sliced zucchini for lasagna noodles. Finish off this cheesy vegetarian casserole with a crispy breadcrumb topping made from almonds to keep it gluten-free.</string>
    <string name="dish16_description">Shrimp and grits are stuffed inside bell peppers and baked in this healthy stuffed peppers recipe. Add the optional hot sauce if you want to give the filling some kick. Look for bell peppers—use any color—with even bottoms so that they stand upright on their own when they are cooked.</string>
    <string name="dish17_description">Do not toss out those almost-past-their-prime vegetables and fresh herbs. Toss them into this skillet egg scramble for a quick vegetarian meal. Nearly any vegetable will work in this easy skillet recipe, so choose your favorites or use what you have on hand.</string>
    <string name="dish18_description">This low-carb burger replaces the typical bun with roasted portobello mushroom caps. Creamy tzatziki and crisp sliced red onion add texture and flavor to this easy Greek-inspired burger recipe.</string>
    <string name="dish19_description">For this quick Thai-inspired curry recipe, we have combined tofu and plenty of veggies with a flavorful sauce made with red curry paste, lime juice and coconut milk. Serve the curry over lightly warmed zucchini noodles to get even more veggies in your weeknight dinner. Bonus: Everything is cooked in one skillet, so there is only one pan to wash after dinner.</string>
    <string name="dish20_description">This healthy chopped salad is a great way to use up leftover cooked chicken. You can reserve the remaining hard-boiled egg half for a snack.</string>
    <string name="dish21_description">This healthy vegetarian take on the Mexican stew pozole gets tons of flavor from poblano peppers, ancho chile powder and dried herbs and spices, while cannellini beans provide protein and fiber.</string>
    <string name="dish22_description">Vegetable gratin recipes often have a crunchy breadcrumb or crouton topping. But summer tomatoes are too gorgeous to hide, so we tucked crusty cubes of bread underneath them instead. Plus, the bread soaks up all the juicy tomato goodness. If you can not find marjoram for this recipe, fresh basil or oregano makes a good substitute.</string>
    <string name="dish23_description">We have taken the key ingredients of a Philly cheesesteak—onions, peppers, thinly sliced beef and provolone cheese—and piled them into portobello mushroom caps to make a meaty and satisfying low-carb main dish.</string>
    <string name="dish24_description">This dish is an easy way to turn grilled vegetables into a satisfying meal, thanks to hearty whole-grain pasta and a quick homemade pesto.</string>
    <string name="dish25_description">This dish is packed with flavor and fits perfectly into a Mediterranean diet.</string>
    <string name="dish26_description">Hummus goes from appetizer to main dish as a rich, tangy coating on chicken breasts. In the oven, the hummus coating caramelizes slightly, and the sprinkle of sesame seeds turns extra-crunchy and nutty. For leftovers, you could slice up the chicken and tuck it into a pita with crisp lettuce, cucumbers and tomatoes.</string>
    <string name="dish27_description">This spaghetti-squash-for-pasta swap slashes both carbs and calories by 75% for a delicious, creamy casserole you can feel good about eating. It is worth roasting the squash versus cooking it in the microwave if you have the time—the flavor gets sweeter and more intense.</string>
    <string name="dish28_description">You do not need broth for this lentil soup recipe—it s rich thanks to the browned bits in the bottom of the pan that meld into the soup, packing it with flavor. Ground coriander, from the seed of the cilantro plant, has a floral, citrusy flavor that dovetails nicely with the lemon.</string>
    <string name="dish29_description">Tender salmon tops a hearty salad of red cabbage, carrots and avocados tossed with a creamy dill vinaigrette in this quick, easy dinner.</string>
    <string name="dish30_description">Chile verde, usually a slow-cooked stew of pork, jalapeños and tomatillos, becomes an easy weeknight meal with quick-cooking ground beef and store-bought green salsa. Make it a Meal: Serve with fresh cilantro, red onion and Monterey Jack. Add cornbread on the side and your favorite hot sauce.</string>
</resources>